{
  "api_job_id": "c7f196e1-5abe-4ca4-90df-e92e2e3d338d",
  "status": "queued",
  "error": null,
  "final_prompt": "The chibi character in a brown beanie and black leather jacket performs a subtle idle breathing loop while facing forward. Her shoulders and long brown hair rise and fall slightly as her body bobs by a few pixels. The movement is rhythmic and calm, with her feet remaining planted as the animation cycles seamlessly.",
  "negative_prompt": "blurry, distorted",
  "animation_type": "other"
}
