{
  "api_job_id": "d948e35e-d50c-403f-8031-ee84ef081fd3",
  "status": "queued",
  "error": null,
  "final_prompt": "The chibi girl in the brown beanie and leather jacket performs a subtle two-frame sleepy idle loop while standing. Her head slumps forward by two pixels as her shoulders drop slightly, accompanied by a slow, rhythmic breathing motion. The animation maintains her front-facing posture and dark sunglasses while conveying a low-energy, drowsy state.",
  "negative_prompt": "blurry, distorted",
  "animation_type": "other"
}
